Sam B. Hall, Jr. Papers, Inclusive: 1943-2005, undated Bulk: 1976-1985
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Committees, 1964-1985; 2
  - Judiciary Committee, 1976-1985; 2
    - Immigration Subcommittee, 1976-1985; 2
      - Immigration Reform Act (HR1510) Hall Amendment, P.M, Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1983, Texas Governor’s Task Force on Immigration (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Legal Services Corporation Act Amendment for Continued Appropriations, H.R. 2909, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Legal Services for Haitians [Legal Services Corporation Authorization], 1983 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Ocean Shipping Act Mark-up H.R. 1878, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Office of Government Ethics Authorization, H.R. 2717, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Private Bills (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Private Bills (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Refugee Act, Hearing, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Refugee Act Re-authorization, Hearing, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Refugee Act Re-authorization, Hearing, H.R. 3195, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Refugee Act Re-authorization, Reports and Background, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Refugee Act reauthorization, Report to Congress, US Catholic Conference, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Agriculture, Education, Labor, Energy, and Commerce Committees’ actions, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Foreign Engineering Students (A.E.A.), 1983 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Full Committee Mark-up, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, 1983 March 1 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, 1983 March 2 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 1, 1983 March 10 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 2, 1983 March 10 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing (1 of 2), 1983 March 10 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing (2 of 2), 1983 March 10 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 1, 1983 March 14 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 2, 1983 March 14 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 1, 1983 March 16 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hearing, Part 2, 1983 March 16 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli Act, H.R. 1510, Interest Group Positions, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Summary and Documents, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Video Copyright Legislation [Home Recording], 1983 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Anti-Crime Act, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Consolidation of Primary Inspections, Subcommittee on Immigration, Refugees, & international law, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - El Salvador Nationals, Temporary Suspension of Deportation, H.R. 4447, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Equal Access, Part 1, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Equal Access, Part 2, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Foreign students, H.R. 1510, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Grounds for Exclusion and Deportation of Aliens, H.R. 4509, 1510 (Immigration and Nationality Act), Mark-up in full committee, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Grounds of Exclusion, H.R. 4509 (Immigration and Nationality Act), Background material, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Immigration Reform and Control Act, Conference Committee Meeting, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1983 (Document), 1984 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Immigration Service Effectiveness, Hearings 98-2, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Judiciary Committee, H.R. 5490, 5656, and 5616, 1984 May 23 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Judiciary Committee, H.R. 4308, 1984 June 19 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Judiciary Committee Agenda, mark-up, 1984 July 31 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Judiciary Committee, H.R. 6012, 6031, 6034, 6067, and 6071, 1984 August 9 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Permanent Residence for Certain Natives of Cuba & Haiti, H.R. 4853 (Cuban -Haitian Adjustment Act), Hearing, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Permanent residence for Cubans, Subcommittee on Immigration, Refugees, & International Law, H.R. 4853, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Salvadoran Refugees, H.R. 4447, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, Conference (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, Conference (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Colleague Letters Received, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Foreign Engineers Educated in the U.S., Hall amendment, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Foreign Engineers, Hall Amendment, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Foreign Students and Engineering Jobs, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hall Amendment (#45) Residence Requirements for foreign engineering students, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Hall Amendment, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Information from Bill Reed, Pres., American Engineering Association (foreign students), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Interagency Cooperation (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Interagency Cooperation (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Printed Material (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Printed Material (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Report No. 98-115, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Small Employers Exemption (Hall), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Social Security Call-in Amendment (Hall), 1984 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, Immigration Reform and Control Act, H.R. 1510, Telephone verification amendment, Hall, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Simpson-Mazzoli, H.R. 1510, Telephone Verification Amendment (Hall), 1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Courts, Liberties, and the Administration of Justice, H.R. 5468, 4307, 4249, 5525, H.J. Res S. 218, 1984 April 27 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on Immigration, Refugees, and International Law, INS Hearings, Budget, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Telephone Verification, H.R. 1510, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Abbreviated Immigration Control bill, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - General Committee Matters, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service Reauthorization, FY86, Hearing (Briefing Book), 1985 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service Reauthorization, FY86, Hearing (briefing book), 1985 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Immigration Reform, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Private bill - Li Cunxin (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Private bill - Li Cunxin (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice Subcommittee, 1977-1982; 3
      - Criminal Code Reform Act (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Criminal Code Reform Act (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Criminal Code, H.R. 6869, Testimony, S. 1437 (New Criminal Code), 1977-1978 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Determinate Sentencing, Corrections Magazine, 1977 September (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Judge Lacey’s Testimony, Grand Jury Reform, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Oral Search Warrants (Telephone Testimony), 1977 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Prohibiting the Sale of Children, H.R. 117, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Removal of Criminal Cases from State to Federal Courts, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Special Prosecutor Legislation, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Special Prosecutor Legislation, H.R. 4292 & S. 555, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Special Prosecutor Legislation, H.R. 2835, 2711, S. 555, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on Criminal Justice, Special Prosecutor Legislation (Hearing report), 1977 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Victims of Crime Act of 1977, H.R. 7010 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Amendment to H.R. 12005, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on Parole of Additional Indochina Refugees, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 2311, 6869, Hearings, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Issue of Sentencing, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Prosecution, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Correspondence, Memos, etc., 1978 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Senate version, S. 1437, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Copy of Tentative Draft of Bill to Revise Criminal Code, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Title 18 offenses Deleted in Proposed Federal Criminal Code, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Various Bills, H.R. 9652, 410, 412, 1956, 5804, & 6488, Also a list of bills relating to service-connected benefits & an agenda for the Comm. on Veterans Affairs Mark-up, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Department of Justice Authorization, Statements, Materials Regarding S. 1437, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Department of Justice Authorization, Statements, Materials Regarding S. 1437, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Department of Justice Authorization, Hearings, FBI H.R. 10400, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, S. 1437/H.R. 6869, Statements & Testimonies, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearings, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 6869 and S.1437, Statements Presented Before Subcommittee on Criminal Justice, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869, Statements, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearings on H.R. 2311 and 6869, Statements and Summaries, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Several Statements Concerning Department of Justice Authorization, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 2311 and 6869, to Revise and Re-codify Federal Criminal Laws, Statements, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearings, H.R. 6869, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Proposed Federal Criminal Code, S. 1437, H.R. 6869, testimony, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearings, H.R. 2311 & 6869, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869, Hearing Witness’ Statements, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Public defenders, H.R. 6869, Includes Testimony from the Federal Public and Community Defenders, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 2311 & 6869, Legislation to Revise Federal Criminal Laws, Hearing, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 & 6869 to Revise Federal Criminal Laws, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869, Statements, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869, Witness’ Statements, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Sentencing Provisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869, statements, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, Hearing on H.R. 2311 and H.R. 6869 to Re-codify Federal Criminal Laws, Copy of H.R. 1559 (Respecting Firearms), 1978 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 6869 & 2311, S. 1437, Testimony, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Criminal Code Revisions, H.R. 6869, for Revision of Criminal Code, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Criminal Justice Subcommittee, Gun Regulations (Hearing report), 1978 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code, Sentencing by Judges. H.R. 7245 included, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Capital Punishment, H.R. 13360 Sentencing in Capital Cases, Statements and Articles & Summaries, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Reform, Smith Act Repeal, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Zurcher v. Standord Daily, Proposal, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - ABA Statement on Criminal Code Reform, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - ABA Report on Proposed Federal Criminal Code, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - ABA, Comments, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - American Civil Liberties Union, Memorandums, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Appointment of Counsel, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Arson, Burglary, & Related Offenses, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Assault Offenses Material, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Attempt, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Attempt & Conspiracy, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Bank of America, Memo of Criminal Code Revision, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Bans to Prosecution, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Bribery & Illegal Gratuity, Official Corruption Offenses, Corporate Slush Funds, Mutiny, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Business Crime, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Child Snatching, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Civil Disabilities, Criminal Record Dissemination, Employment Disabilities, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Class Actions, Civil Proceeding, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Comments, Justice Deptartment, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Commitment of Mentally Ill Defendants, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Contempt Offenses, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Counterfeiting, Forgery, and Related Offenses, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Criminal Conspiracy, Background Information, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Criminal Division Oversight (Justice Department) 96-1, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Defense Department, Comments, 1979 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Drug Offenses (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Drug Offenses (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Duress and Necessity, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Espionage, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Espionage and related Offenses, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - Explosives and Firearms, Weapons on an Aircraft, Use of a Weapon in a Crime, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Extortion (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Extortion (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - False Statement Offenses, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Federal Criminal Jurisdiction, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Foreign Affairs/Neutrality Provisions, Background, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Foreign Relations, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Functional Analysis of the Criminal Code Reform Act of 1978, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Gambling, Sexual Exploitation of Children, and Obscenity, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - General, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - General Assistant to the Attorney General Statement, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Immigration Offenses, Murder and Assault, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Immigration, Naturalization, and Passports, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Indian Country Jurisdiction, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Insanity Defense Code, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Insanity Defense, Various Materials, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Insanity Defense, Criminal Code Revision, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Juvenile Crime, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Kidnapping, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Meetings, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Memorandum from Counsel, Criminal Code Reform, by date, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Minutes, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, News Articles, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Multiple Prosecutions, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - National Alliance Against Racism, Comments, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - National Defense and Related Offenses (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - National Defense and Related Offenses (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 85, Folder 10)
      - Obscenity, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 11)
      - Obscenity, Broadcasting, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 12)
      - Obstruction of Government, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - Obstruction of Justice, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - Obstruction of Law Enforcement, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 15)
      - Organized Crime, Racketeering, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 16)
      - Perjury, False Statements, and Related Offenses, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Perjury and Fraud, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Political Process Offenses (Obstructing Elections), 1979 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Privacy, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Privacy and Eavesdropping, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Probation, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Prostitution, Gambling, Failing to Obey a Public Safety Order, Criminal Code Revision, Labor and Sports Bribery, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Public Corruption, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Public Duty Defense, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Real Property, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Restriction, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Rules Enabling Acts, Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure, Appellate Procedure, and Evidence, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Sabotage and Related Offenses, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - Securities, Monetary, Commodity, Exchange, and Antitrust Offenses, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Self-defense and Official Misstatement of Law, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Sentencing and Parole (1 of 4), 1979 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Sentencing and Parole (2 of 4), 1979 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Sentencing and Parole (3 of 4), 1979 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Sentencing and Parole (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Sentencing (1 of 5), 1979 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Sentencing (2 of 5), 1979 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Sentencing (3 of 5), 1979 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Sentencing (4 of 5), 1979 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Sentencing (5 of 5) (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Sentencing Issues, Part III Criminal Code Revision, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Sentencing and Corrections General Provisions, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Sex Offenses, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Smuggling/Trafficking, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Statutes of Limitations, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Treason, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Theft and Related Offenses, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Whistle Blowers (Senate-passed bill), section 1525, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - White Collar Crime (H.R. 6869), 1979 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Victims of Crime Compensation, Statements, Hearings, Reports, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      - Victims of Crime Mark-up, H.R. 1899, Bill to Help States Assist Innocent Victims of Crime, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Victims of Crime Mark-up and Proposed Recodification of Federal Criminal Laws, 1978-79 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Victims of Crime, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - ACLU Comments, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Amendments, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Amendment in Committee, H.R. 6915, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Appeal of Sentences, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Bribery, Fraud, and Theft, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Citizens’ Commission on Human Rights, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Commerce Department, Comments, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Committee Consideration, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Committee Memos, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Committee Print, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Complicity, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Counsel in Grand Jury Room, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revision Subcommittee, Notes, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revision, HOBBS Act Amendments (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Criminal Code Revision, HOBBS Act Amendment (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Defenses, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Endangerment, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure, Peremptory Challenge of a Judge (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure, Peremptory Challenge of a Judge (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Memorandum from Counsel, Criminal Code Reform, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Railroad, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Robbery, Extortion, and Blackmail, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Sentencing Guidelines, Alternatives, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Sentencing, Penalties, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - States of Mind, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Treasury Department, Commerce, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - American Bar Association Views, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - American Builders and Contractor's Views, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - American Civil Liberties Union Views, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Association of General Contractors Views, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Bail Reform, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Criminal Code Reform, General, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Defenders, Views, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - Department of Justice, Views and Comments, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Father Drinan’s Comments, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Gun Control, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 13)
      - Hobbs Act Amendment, Teamsters, H.R. 115, 450, 3047 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      - Hobbs Act Amendment (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Hobbs Act Amendment (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Hobbs Act Amendment (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Jurisdiction over U.S. Nationals Abroad, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Labor Extortion, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - NAAG Views, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Mental Incompetency, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - NORML, Marijuana Laws, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Organized Crime Proposals, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Public Service Research Council, Views & comments, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Racial Violence, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Racially Motivated Violence, Hearing, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Racial Violence Hearings, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Railway Labor (views), 1981 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - SEARCH Reports, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Sentencing, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Sports Violence, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Teamsters, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Criminal Code Revision Committee Memo, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Criminal Code Revision, General Comments, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Crime Control and Victims’ Compensation Act, H.R. 7001, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Hobbs Act Incidents, Specific Incidents, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Hobbs Act Amendment, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Insanity Defense Bills, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Judicial Conference Views, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Prison Fellowship Views and Comments, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Schedules, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Sensenbrenner’s Substitute, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Criminal Code Mark-up [Sentencing and corrections] H.R. 1647, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Administrative Law and Governmental Relations, 1978-1985; 4
      - HR 7679, Providing for Direct Action Diplomat Insurers Entitled to Immunity in the U.S. Courts, and H.R. 11002 (contract disputes), 1978 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Summaries and testimony on H.R. 9219, Federal Tort Claims Act Amendment, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Regulation Reform Act of 1980, H.R. 3263 (1 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Regulation Reform Act of 1980, H.R. 3263 (2 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Claims, H.R. 594, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)